[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the end line of Margaret Mitchels only novel and of the self-titled Academy Award-winning movie adaptation?", "correct_answer": "After all, tomorrow is another day.", "incorrect_answers": ["Frankly, my dear, I dont give a damn.", "So, you see I shall have to marry you.", "Ill go home. And Ill think of some way to get him back."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The movie Pirates of the Caribbean: The Curse of the Black Pearl was directed by Gore Verbinski and produced by Jerry Bruckheimer.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In this horror movie a six-year-old boy, named Michael Myers, is locked in a mental institution after brutally killing his older sister.", "correct_answer": "Halloween", "incorrect_answers": ["Wrong Turn", "Jeepers Creepers", "Amityville"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In mathematics, what type of conic section would this equation show: x^2+y^2=9?", "correct_answer": "Circle", "incorrect_answers": ["Secant", "Line", "Ray"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In this 1992 movie, directed by Charles Robert Carner, two girls take their pretty friend to a creek, where they torture and finally kill her.", "correct_answer": "A Killer Among Friends", "incorrect_answers": ["A Friendship To Die For", "A Kidnapping In The Family", "Friends Till The End"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What did the Byzantine empresses do in the Purple Chamber?", "correct_answer": "Give Birth", "incorrect_answers": ["Have their wedding night", "Rest in to be seen by others during their final days of life", "Get Married"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Spanish painter and sculptor Pablo Picasso is known for co-founding what art movement?", "correct_answer": "Cubism", "incorrect_answers": ["Expressionism", "Surrealism", "Neorealism"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what U.S. state is the famous Bridalveil Fall located?", "correct_answer": "California", "incorrect_answers": ["Florida", "Colorado", "Hawaii"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "At the of the movie The Great Escape, the Germans took prisoners out of the truck and shot them. How many were said to be shot?", "correct_answer": "50", "incorrect_answers": ["25", "13", "20"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The physicians in this country can opt for education in aromatherapy, which would allow them to prescribe essential oils in their medical practice.", "correct_answer": "France", "incorrect_answers": ["Germany", "Switzerland", "Greece"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who did Allie Hamilton meet while working as a nurse in the 2004 romance film The Notebook?", "correct_answer": "her future fiance Lon Hammond", "incorrect_answers": ["her old flame Noah Calhoun", "none of these", "her future fiance and eventual husband Lon Hammond"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the last name of Shirley MacLaines character in Terms of Endearment?", "correct_answer": "Greenway", "incorrect_answers": ["Nicholas", "Francini", "Williamson"]}]